hey brother so here's some here's the
here's the quick answer to your question
that you're asking me that question is
already your answer and I don't think
I'm doing that to hide my own hide my
own non glowing on reflection or not but
um or if it's a or if I'm actually onto
something
so consider and here's the thing I want
you to to get at that is like and and
and give me your answer to this watch
your video
similarly why you said to me it's
similarly to the one the way that you've
been watching mark and i's riffs
watching watch it a couple of times and
and think about this question and then
in and tell me what you what you see or
what the question elucidates for you
what is it that you here's the question
what is it that you understand about
what you don't know and what you're
asking about that allows you to know
that you don't understand so what are
you doing like what what do you already
understand about what you don't know
that allows you to see that you don't
know that did then ask the question so
if that might just watch your own your
own question to me a few times then get
back to me